翻译，压制：布尔
字体：思源黑体 Medium
Hi guys.
大家好
Hey we're 'Shoptimus Prime which is the barbershop quartet that was featured in Cuphead.
我们是'Shoptimus Prime 也就是在茶杯头中演出过的那个理发店四重唱
You found our fourth member in the game.
你在游戏中找到了我们中的第四个成员
Now it's time to learn to sing a little bit of barbershop on your own.
现在是时候来学一点理发店四重唱了
So in barbershop we have four parts.
在理发店四重唱中分为四个部分
We've got the tenor, the lead, the baritone and the bass.
我们有高音 主唱 中音还有低音
The lead singing the melody. That's me.
主唱负责主旋律的部分
We've got the bass anchoring the sound.
低音用来支撑主旋律
We've got the tenor harmonizing above the lead.
高音在主旋律之上进行协调
And then we got the baritone harmonizing in the middle
然后中音负责中间部分的协调
just kind of doing the filling parts.
有点像是补充各部分之间的不足
So here's how we broke it down in the game.
这是我们在游戏中插曲的分解部分
In the lead part.
主唱的部分
Why not take a little quick break
为何不快快休息一下
Then come back for more
然后回来继续玩
Please come back for more
请你回来继续玩
Bass.
低音的部分
Why not take a little quick break
为何不快快休息一下
Then come back for more
然后回来继续玩
Please come back for more
请你回来继续玩
And the baritone goes like this.
然后是中音的部分
Why not take a little quick break
为何不快快休息一下
Then come back for more
然后回来继续玩
Please come back for more
请你回来继续玩
And the tenor.
接着是高音的部分
Why not take a little quick break
为何不快快休息一下
Then come back for more
然后回来继续玩
Please come back for more
请你回来继续玩
This is what it sounds like when we put it all together.
接下来是合在一起的效果
Why not take a little quick break
为何不快快休息一下
Then come back for more
然后回来继续玩
Please come back for more
请你回来继续玩
Alright, go out.
好吧 出去
Sing some barbershop on your own.
自己试试吧
Thanks guys! Thanks!
谢谢大家
注: 这句话是boss战开场旁白之一，其他台词详见cuphead.fandom.com/wiki/Announcer
A brawl is surely brewing.
气氛逐渐蕉焦灼了起来